thetop10sites.com 2014-07-01

# Privacy Policy - TheTop10Sites

**The Top 10 Sites Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 2014 and supersedes all earlier versions of our Privacy Policy.

We at TheTop10Sites.com take our customers’ privacy seriously. The following document details our privacy policy and explains what personal information, if at all, we collect on our users, and how we could potentially utilize it. That having been said, TheTop10Sites.com employs many measures to ensure that your information remain as secure and confidential as possible. 

For more information please review our Terms of Use.

**Please Note - Using our site and services will indicate that you have read, as well as accepted, this Privacy Policy. We ask that you read our Privacy Policy with care and that you use our services if, and only if, you agree with our terms and conditions.**

TheTop10Sites.com’s registered address is: Wickham’s Cay II, P.O. Box 2221, Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin Islands If you have any related data protection queries please feel free to contact us via mail at: Info at TheTop10Sites.com.

TheTop10Sites uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.

When you register and/or use our services we reserve the right to collect your personal information. For example, when you sign up in order to write a review we will check to make sure it is you by sending an email confirmation to your signup mail account. We will save this mail in our database to identify you in your next login and to get in touch with you if you should wish it.

Also, while you take advantage of the services we offer, services such as various website comparisons, we may store information including how you use the site: e.g. pages viewed, where you were linked to us from, etc. However we will never ask you for personal financial data such as bank account or payment details.

TheTop10Sites.com will periodically review the personal information stored in its database, in order to ensure that we comply with the law and that said information is kept no longer than is permitted.

**Use of Information**  
TheTop10Sites.com may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  1. To enable you to access and use our services; and/or 
  2. To communicate with you if you wish it by asking us to send you notifications and updates, including sending you information about products and services which we think may be of interest to you.

Passing on information 

Part of using our services means you consent to us disclosing some of your personal information, if necessary, to third parties.

Third-party vendors, including Google, may show your ads on sites across the Internet. TheTop10Sites and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to your website.

**Sending you Information and Updates**

By using our services, you agree that we are entitled to send you information via e-mail, post or twits. Information may include products, services and offers we think may interest you.

That said, customers will always be able to request that marketing content not be sent to them anymore, meaning that you are consenting to such use, unless you inform us otherwise. Also, we will make sure that all of the marketing materials sent to you via mail/social media will include subscription cancelling instructions.

If you do decide to unsubscribe, you can always contact our customer service via mail at support@TheTop10Sites.com

**Constantly Improving our Services**

In an attempt to ensure that the services we provide continue to fit all of your needs, we will periodically ask you for feedback. Feel free to write us what's on your mind and we'll try to improve accordingly. We will not publish any of your feedback without your written consent.

**Cookies**

To enhance your experience we are using web cookies, which are tiny text files placed on your browser. \We do delete most of our cookies as soon as you close your browser, while some are stored away until deleted or expired. This can be done via your browser, however blocking or deleting cookies might cause our services to become impaired or less accessible. By using our services, you consent to us using cookies.    

**Security**

Our website uses SSL certificates and encryption methods as keeping your information secure is of the utmost importance to us. Keep in mind that data transmission over the internet can never be fully secure. Though sensitive information such as your password will be encrypted, a method that minimizes the risk of having your information stolen, there is always some risk involved in uploading your information online, and any information you upload or input is done so at your own risk.

**Feedback**

We greatly appreciate your thoughts and ideas. Feel free to contact us via the feedback button or via eMail: Support at TheTop10Sites.com
